In this section, there are three things that we are told. In the next section, we are told that we are transparent like never before.
Okay, we are transparent, but I don't think we should do an entire slide.
Because there is nothing else.
I mean, this is just a self-explanatory point.
We are told our own qualities.
Now, we are told how different we are or what are the benefits of us.
Now, we are told that we are like brothers.
Maybe we don't need this section.
Or we can add this section later.
Or we can try to do it in a different way.
And there is a sentence in it.
So you find what works for you with no surprises.
You don't have to add anything.
With no surprises, you don't have to add anything.
Zero commission, zero bias.
We have already said this.
Now we are talking about a story.
So these are the three new information.
We don't take commission.
We don't have bias for any bank.
And our banking is genuine.
These are the three new information.
You can look through everything on your own pace.
We have already given you some information.
You can look through.
So it's not even half information.
It's half genuine.
So you won't get spam calls.
But if you don't have spam calls, it's okay.
You can add it on your own pace.
We have already added it.
You can look through.
Without giving your phone number.
If you look through, it will take a few seconds.
You don't have to do that.
But this is the new information.
You won't get spam calls.
And you don't have to sell anything.
You can get documents.
And you don't have to give any notification.
You won't get spam calls.
But this is the part.
How to change the market.
We have standardized everything.
And we bring everything to you.
And you have to do everything.
And this is the part.
Who is going to call you?
If you don't take it, who is going to call you?
Yes.
This is the part.
And you pick the banks.
Apply once.
This is the new information.
Look at the net.
These four points are good.
But if you give these four texts.
It can be a concern.
But the transparent is in the middle.
Even if we tell everyone that we are transparent.
Like never before.
We will look for it.
These are the three points.
We are really unique.
So now we have six unique points.
And we are not unique in the first half.
And we can accommodate the second half.
We have six unique points so far.
But we are not accommodating the top.
Basically, this is how it was made.
If we put everything in one place.
Then it becomes heavy onwards.
So it is not a separate section.
Now we will tell you six things in total.
So what we have to do is.
We have to make a story in those six.
And we have to refactor it.
Make a slide of these two.
Make a slide of these three.
And make a slide of the last point.
Something like this.
The analogy of four sections.
And the analogy of six points.
How many sections do we divide?
We have to refactor the story.
Basically, one screen does not take too many words.
Yes, yes.
Six points.
And how many minimum words are needed for each point?
And which points go together?
And how do these flow into each other?
Without making this home page long.
By reducing section.
The goal of entire activity is consolidation.
Whatever you are making, we have to increase it.
We have to reduce it.
This is also the same.
I was making it years later.
Let me build it.
Overall, I like the font, color guide, sections and spacing.
I like it a lot.
I have changed my website.
In the beginning...
In the beginning, when I was explaining, I used to feel like I am missing something.
When I was explaining, I used to feel like I am missing something.
You were at 5, I was telling you to come at 20, and you got me at 60.
60 was not in my mind.
It was in my mind.
The color is not white.
It is nice.
The color is not there.
The whole section is fading away.
From the start, it was not like that.
I think we should remove this section.
Actually, I would say we should remove the voice chat.
And fit it.
It is not opening up.
I see one line.
I have to read more.
I see only one point on one screen.
Then I can read it.
Maybe we should remove this section.
It would be unique.
I don't know if you can see this.
It is not just words.
No, it is not in the phone.
It is not in the phone.
It is below the drop down.
It is just a duplicate.
We should put it here.
And it will scroll.
It is cheap.
Many companies do it.
I have seen it.
Apple doesn't do it.
Yes.
Even if they have kept it.
It is not normal.
I don't know how to do it.
I can't do it.
And when we compare.
Actually I have seen it.
But it is written on the top.
It is not seen on the top.
What is the difference?